<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="Welcome">Welcome to Trigger Buster!</string>
    <string name="Done">High Score</string>
    <string name="Quote">"It will take your breath away"</string>
    <string name="Game">"This is the game"</string>
    <string name="app_name">Trigger Busters</string>
    <string name="StartGameBoy">Start Game Boy</string>
    <string name="StartGameGirl">Start Game Girl</string>
    <string name="ScorePoints">Click here to score points!</string>
    <string name="EndGame">Exit</string>
    <string name="MainScreen">Main Screen</string>
    <string name="Rules">See rules</string>
     <string name="DisplayRules">The city is filled with dust and it\'s your job to clean it all up!
Use the arrow keys to move around the city and pick up the dust pieces along the way.
Watch out for the asthma triggers though. The pet, mold, cockroach, and cigarette will chase you all around the board.
You start with two inhalers and one nebulizer. Every time you get hit by a trigger, you need to take a puff.
After two inhaler puffs, if you get hit, it\'s time to use the nebulizer.
One more hit after you use your nebulizer means a game over so be careful!
See if you can beat your high score!
Good luck!!!</string>
    <item name="Score" type="integer">0</item>
    <string name="collision_message">You have been hit! Now, you need to take a puff from your inhaler.</string>
    <string name="collision_message_pet">You have been hit by a cat! Keep your pet out of your bedroom! Now, you need to take a puff from your inhaler.</string>
    <string name="collision_message_mold">You have been hit by mold! Be sure to check your leaking pipes! Now, you need to take a puff from your inhaler.</string>
    <string name="collision_message_cockroach">You have been hit by a cockroach! Get a cockroach trap and ask them to check into the roach motel! Now, you need to take a puff from your inhaler.</string>
    <string name="collision_message_smoke2">You have been hit by smoke! Don\'t let people smoke around you! Now, you need to take a puff from your inhaler.</string>
	<string name="collision_message_smoke3">You have been hit by smoke! Don\'t let people smoke in your car! Now, you need to take a puff from your inhaler.</string>
    <string name="collision_message_smoke">You have been hit by smoke! Don\'t let people smoke in your house! Now, you need to take a puff from your inhaler.</string>
    <string name="collision_message2">You have been hit! Because you have used your inhaler twice, it\'s time for the nebulizer.</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="inhaler_message1">Take your daily medicine so you can go enjoy your day!</string>
    <string name="inhaler_message2">Now that you have taken your daily medicine you can begin the game!</string>
	<string name="startgame">                    Click on a character to begin!</string>
	<string name="Up">U</string>
	<string name="Down">D</string>
	<string name="Left">L</string>
	<string name="Right">R</string>
	<string name="Pause">Pause</string>
</resources>